Welcome back to VS Code. We're going to
be spending a lot of time in here this
week. Bring up your favorite terminal
with control back tick. It's the only
terminal. I don't know be your favorite
terminal, but whatever. Your terminal.
Bring it up and then go into your into
your home directory and into your
projects directory. And you're going to
do a git clone of just a sort of basic
scaffolding I've got in place for you.
Here it is. It's the project is called
finally. Finally, because it's our final
week. It's when we're going multi- aent
and it's also finally because that
stands for finance ally. We're going to
build a live trader workstation with
cool market data and stuff happening and
it's going to feel like a high-end
application and we're going to do it
with an army of agents. We're going to
do it all this week. It's in this this
repo finally clone it and then open it
up as a new project and I will see you
there. Okay. So, you open it up as a
project by by going over project and
then going into projects finally. And
it's showing you now. And it should look
something like this. There might be more
files in here cuz I'm I'm sort of
figuring out how much I want to give you
as a starting point. And we're going to
work on some of this together. We're
going to set up a whole foundation that
we can then give to a bunch of agents to
build the whole project for us in as
much of a like a oneshot experience as
we can do. But let me just talk you
through it. Close everything down. Let
me show you what we've got here. So in
in finally your starting point should
look something like this. There is a uh
the usual there's an emptyish readme.
There's a claude.mmd that we'll go
through in a second. There's a bunch of
directories that are empty that may not
even show up for you because they're
empty like a backend db front end. These
are all completely empty. And there's
one called planning which has a single
document plan.md.
And then there's also an empty test. All
right. That's the uh there's a there's a
useful git ignore and then there's the
of course the claw.md that we will look
at now and there's also f file where I
put my open routter key in there just
copied it from before okay into the
claw.md it's very short finally project
the finance ally finally I'm probably
not the first person to think of that uh
but still it works nicely for this this
project uh and it just says all project
documentation is in the planning
directory this is that point I made
about one of the the stabilizing forces
is to get all of your different coding
agents to be converging on shared
documentation which is where they can
leave information for each other to to
keep them all communicating closely. The
key document is in plan.mmd included in
full here. And then I'm using that at
notation as a way of ensuring that this
entire document gets brought into
context every time. It has no choice. So
it all sort of revolves around this
plan. MD and this is going to be our
tool for how we control the build of the
whole application. And so this this
document which I'll open in preview mode
so we see it nice and formatted. This is
going to be our business requirements.
That is what I want us to build. And the
first stage is us building this out so
that it feels like it's robust. So the
vision is that we're building a stunning
AI powered trading workstation. It
doesn't matter if you don't know about
financial services. This is still going
to make sense to you. If you know what
stocks and shares are, that's that's all
you need. It's going to stream live
market data. It's going to let users
trade in a simulated portfolio and it's
going to integrate an LLM assistant that
can analyze portfolios and execute
trades on your behalf. It looks and
feels like a modern Bloomberg terminal
with an AI co-pilot which could be a
whole product in its own. This could be
a real for reals product. And I say in
this vision that it's the capstone
project for the course built entirely by
coding agents demonstrating how
orchestrated agents can produce a
production quality full stack
application inter agents interact
through files in the planning directory
that lays the lays the scene out there
for for you and also for the AI agents.
Okay. And I should confess that I
started with a paragraph like that and I
just put it in in actually in Claude in
Claude.ai AI the chatbot and iterated a
bit for most of the rest of this. So
most of the rest of this is just based
on generated but from some question and
answering with me which is a good way to
do it. You could also do it in cloud
code but but I chose just to use the
chat product. So the user experience
explains that it's all going to run in
in Docker that it will a browser will
open to local host and that you'll be
able to then uh do things like watch
prices stream monitor the portfolio chat
with an AI assistant. There's a bit
about the visual design and the usual
color scheme that I like but you should
put in your own color scheme. This
architecture thing here was generated of
course by by Claude uh and it's very
clear that there are some some roots
explained here. We're going to very
consistent with how we've done some of
the prior projects use SQL light. Um
we're going to have like a background
task for market data. Okay. And then
there's some explanation as to why the
directory structure is laid out there
and it's consistent with what's already
been set up and there's some stuff about
the boundaries between areas because as
you can imagine we're going to be
looking into having multiple coding
agents working on different parts. So
focusing on the boundaries is really
important because agents need to know
what they're responsible for and and how
they have to interact with each other.
Next section explains about the
environment variables that there's going
to be uh an open route API key which
which uh you already have and then
optionally an API key to something
called massive formerly known as polygon
that I cover in some of my other
courses. It's optional because the idea
is you don't need to have real market
data because this product will include a
simulated market data. So, it can be
just as cool without having to pay a
scent. You can see everything going on
as if it's a live market. And that can
be a great way to build out trading
agents, equity traders, because you want
to see how they respond to simulated
data as well as the real thing. Uh but
you'll be able should should you wish to
pay for proper equity market data or
even crypto or options or whatever you
like you should be able to switch that
in with an API key change. Okay. And
then that's all explained in this next
section on market data explaining that
there's two different options and
explaining how we will use SSE approach
the same way that information is
streamed back when you're working with
an AI as a way of streaming back market
data live onto the user interface. And
then we're going simple with the
database. We're going to use SQL light
as before, lazily set up the first time
you launch the app. A little bit more
sophisticated than last week that it's
going to persist between sessions as as
you can see if you read through it. Uh
but still quite simplistic, but it
should be an easy task to upgrade this
to use like a a database like superbase.
So it's an API based Postgress database
on the cloud if you wish to. But we'll
keep it simple for this because we're
trying to build the app, not necessarily
worry about sort of third party
integrations. Bit more on the API
endpoints. And then more about the LLM
integration. We're going to use the same
Cerebrass approach or open router
approach because I love the way it's so
fast. You don't need to use Cerebrass if
you don't want to. And we're going to
use structured outputs just as we did in
week two. So we can have an interactive
conversation with an LLM and allow it to
do things like make trading decisions
and change the way that the user
interface looks. So that's all part of
how this is explained. And you can see
that I've included a dot claude and I've
just copied in the cerebrass skill that
we made in week two. So we're just
taking that same skill again. So we've
got the skill, it can use it right away.
We know how that works. We know that
just by putting that folder in there,
it's just going to have this new skill.
That's the the the crazy thing about
skills and stuff about how it will
execute automatically. Uh this reads a
little bit LLM generated, but it doesn't
matter. It's fine. And then front-end
design, how the screens will be laid
out. I chatted with Claude a while about
this to make sure that I was happy with
it. And then the way that it's all going
to be deployed super simply in one
Docker container, just as we did last
week, it's a really easy pattern. LLMs
love to try and put things into multiple
Docker containers and make it more
complicated than it needs to be. This is
why it did that to start with and I came
in and said, "No, that's not necessary.
We don't need it." That's the kind of of
place where human involvement is so
important. And it can be hard for people
that aren't familiar with these kinds of
architectures and you just have to
really challenge yourself to ask the
pointed questions of could this be
simpler. Make sure that it is as simple
as possible. All right? And then uh how
how we'll be able to start and stop. And
one one of the great benefits of having
it all be in one docker container like
this is it also means that should you
wish we can easily deploy it to the
cloud. We could easily just just take
this and put it up there uh on a hugging
face space perhaps or even deployed to
AWS apprunner or something like that
ways that we cover on my production
course if you wish to go live with this
afterwards. And then finally stuff about
how we will test it with unit tests and
end toend tests. That is the
documentation. That is the business
requirements docs slightly fleshed out
with Claude. Uh and it is our starting
point for the finally project. a juicy
great big project which is going to feel
immensely satisfying and which as much
as possible we're going to try and run
using multiple agents in controlled
chaos. Yes.